Say neighbor acknowledge God, for what He had done!
Come on, put your hands together for Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Some body bless the name of the Lord. Come on church!
Acknowledge God for what He has done.
He will do it again.
Come on bless the name of the Lord.
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Acknowledge God for what He has done.
He will do it again.
Sing: Acknowledge God!
Acknowledge God for what He has done.
He will do it again.
Sing: Acknowledge God.
Acknowledge God for what He has done.
He will do it again.
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Are you happy?
Acknowledge God for the role He's been playing.
He will do it again.
He will do it again. Sing: Acknowledge God.
Acknowledge God for the role He's been playing.
Because He will do it again.
Say: Acknowledge God.
Acknowledge God for the role He's been playing.
Because He will do it again.
Someone clap your hands. Is someone happy?
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
Cry no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
Complain no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
Sing: cry no more.
Cry no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
complain no more.
Complain no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
Sing: cry no more
Cry no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
Complain no more!
Complain no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
One more time sing: cry no more.
Cry no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
Sing: complain no more!
Complain no more. Acknowledge God, He will do it again.
Faith has done it.
God has done it.
He is the healer, the healer, defender, provider.
He is the savior, the savior, deliverer, defender
God has done it.
Faith has done it.
He is the healer, the healer, defender, provider.
God has done it.
He is the savior, the savior, defender, way maker.
He is my healer, your healer, defender, provider.
God has done it.
Faith has done it
Faith has done it.
God has done it.
faith has done it.
Faith has done it.
God has done it.
Faith has has done it.
Faith has done it.
God has done it.
TT: Esther Mwelwa 12/23/18